<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meet In Paris</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_main">DateTimePicker Example</string>
    <string name="selected_time">The time you picked will be shown here.</string>
    <string name="selected_date">The date you picked will be shown here.</string>
    <string name="selected_datetime">The date and time you picked will be shown here.</string>
    <string name="pick_time">Pick Time</string>
    <string name="pick_date">Pick Date</string>
    <string name="pick_datetime">Pick Date+Time</string>
    <string name="mode_24_hours">Use 24 hour mode</string>
    <string name="mode_dark">Use dark theme</string>
    <string name="mode_custom_accent">Use custom accent</string>
    <string name="vibrate">Vibrate on touch</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss on pause (eg: orientation change)</string>
    <string name="title">Show a title</string>
    <string name="show_version_2">Use marshmallow layout</string>
    <string name="show_year_first">Show the year picker first</string>
    <string name="enable_seconds">Show seconds picker</string>
    <string name="enable_minutes">Show minutes picker</string>
    <string name="limit_times">Limit selectable times</string>
    <string name="limit_dates">Limit selectable dates</string>
    <string name="disable_dates">Disable specific dates</string>
    <string name="highlight_dates">Highlight certain dates</string>

    <string name="tab_title_time">Time</string>
    <string name="tab_title_date">Date</string>
    <string name="tab_title_datetime">Date+Time</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="random_text">Ye to misery wisdom plenty polite to as. Prepared interest proposal it he exercise.
        My wishing an in attempt ferrars. Visited eat you why service looking engaged. At place no walls hopes rooms fully in.
        Roof hope shy tore leaf joy paid boy.Noisier out brought entered detract because sitting sir. Fat put occasion rendered off humanity has.
        Bringing so sociable felicity supplied mr. September suspicion far him two acuteness perfectly. Covered as an examine so regular of.
        Ye astonished friendship remarkably no. Window admire matter praise you bed whence. Delivered ye sportsmen zealously arranging frankness estimable as.
        Nay any article enabled musical shyness yet sixteen yet blushes. Entire its the did figure wonder off.
        Wise busy past both park when an ye no. Nay likely her length sooner thrown sex lively income. The expense windows adapted sir.
        Wrong widen drawn ample eat off doors money. Offending belonging promotion provision an be oh consulted ourselves it.
        Blessing welcomed ladyship she met humoured sir breeding her. Six curiosity day assurance bed necessary.
</string>
</resources>
